# Rini Fajarwati

Yogyakarta, Indonesia | Phone: +62 812 5565 5012

Email: rinifajarwati20@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/rini-fajarwati | github.com/rinifajarwati

#### **SUMMARY**

A graduate of Informatics from Ahmad Dahlan University (UAD) who has experience in website development and data processing. Able to work together in a team, good communication, critical thinking, and familiarity with PHP, Laravel, Python, also database processing using MySQL. I am determined to apply the gained knowledge practically to deliver the best results.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# IT Programmer Internship | PT. Prima Indo Medilab

Mei 2023 - Juli 2023

- Analyze data needs.
- Responsible for creating a full stack web based on client requests.
- create data management starting from employee data, employee self service, and development people.
- Successfully created a Human Resource Information System (HRIS) website using Laravel, JavaScript, and MySQL (Laragon).

# Informatics Laboratory Assistant | Ahmad Dahlan University

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022

- Train 50+ students to solve problems and understand statistics course material in the laboratory.
- Report learning outcomes at the end of the semester to the lecturer.

#### **PROJECT**

# Web Developer | Ahmad Dahlan University

Sep 2021 - Jul 2022

- Analyze data needs.
- Responsible for creating a full stack web based on client requests.
- Successfully created a system for predicting students faculty of timely industrial technology using Python, Flask and MySql.

# Web Developer | SDN 001 Tanjung Selor

Nov 2020 - Feb 2021

- Analyze data needs.
- Responsible for creating a full stack web based on client requests.
- Successfully created a SDN 001 Tanjung Selor profile website using HTML, PHP, CSS, and MySQL.

# ORGANIZATION AND ACTIVITIES

# Informasi and communication division staff (KOMINFO) | Student Association of Informatics UAD

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

- Responsible for the implementation of the seminar program Seminar Melawan Hoax made by the organization.
- Responsible for managing Instagram content and disseminating information via WhatsApp.

# **EDUCATION**

# Ahmad Dahlan University, Yogyakarta Bachelor of Computer Science / GPA: 3.63

2018 - 2022

Honor: Cum Laude

#### **SKILLS**

# Hard Skills:

- PHP
- MySQL
- Laravel
- Postgresql
- Bootstrap
- Laragon
- Flask
- Python
- JavaOuarkus
- Postman

## **Soft Skills:**

- Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Teamwork
- Problem Solving